Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. International Offices Records, 1929-1998 and undated RL.00716
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Audiovisual Materials, 1992-1995 and undated, 2 boxes
  - Brazil (Box 31)
    - AV2. Cigarros Minister, Continental spots. Format: VHS. Undated. (Box 31)
  - Ecuador
    - AV3. TV Commercials, Historical Reel. Format: Umatic. Date: 1992 Sept. (Box 31)
      [Includes spots for Durex, Lotto, Kodak, Mastercard, Hall's, Top Cream, Salsa de Tomate, Sonapal, among others.]
  - India
    - AV4. Pepsi's Touching Tribute to Kapil Dev. Format: Betacam. Undated. (Box 31)
  - Latin America
    - AV5. Rolo Histórico Farinha Láctea. Format: VHS. Date: 1992. (Box 31)
    - AV6. Rolo Histórico Lux Luxo. Format: VHS. Date: 1992. (Box 31)
    - AV7. Rolo Histórico Nescau. Format: VHS. Date: 1992. (Box 31)
    - AV8. Rolo Histórico Neston. Format: VHS. Date: 1992. (Box 31)
  - Mexico
    - AV9. Christmas Party for Mexican Employees. Format: Umatic. Date: 1994. (Box 31)
    - AV10. Commercial Presentation Reel. Format: Umatic. Date: 1995 May 24. (Box 32)
      [Includes spots for Kellogg's, Warner Lambert, Kodak, Nestlé, Nabisco, Oscar Mayer, Pizza Hut, Ford.]
    - AV11. Holmes Radio Interview. Format: Audio Cassette. Undated. (Box 32)
    - AV12. Various Comerciales, Reel Historico. Format: Umatic. Date: 1992 Sept. 23. (Box 32)
  - Montreal
    - AV13. Historical Reel. Format: Umatic. Date: 1992. (Box 32)
      [Includes spots for Red Rose Tea, Pepsi and French version of commercial JWT Does That.]
  - Philippines
    - AV14. Showreel, Satellite Wars. Format: VHS. Date: 1993 Jun. 4. (Box 32)
  - Puerto Rico
    - AV15. Pelicula: Pabellon de Sevilla. Format: Umatic. Date: 1992 Sept. 23. (Box 32)
  - Uruguay
    - AV16. Untitled. Format: Betacam. Undated. (Box 32)
- Restricted Materials, 1 box
  RESTRICTED: Unpublished materials are closed to non-JWT researchers for 15 years from date of creation.
  - Colombia (Box 33)
    - Internal document explaining how to obtain international information through JWT network, 1998 (Box 33)
    - Local work for Ford and Chicle Adams clients, 1997 (Box 33)
    - Vision document prepared by James Evans, 1997 (Box 33)
  - Poland (Warsaw Office), Polish Society and Consumer Characteristics, 1996 Nov. (Box 33)